TERRY KIM

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER

INFO

Address 5057 Maplewood

Ave. #PH3, Los Angeles, 90004, United States

Phone (213)-500-5906

Email <u>terry.javascript@gmail.com</u>

DATE / PLACE OF BIRTH

1993-07-02

Seoul, South Korea

NATIONALITY

American

SOCIAL PROFILES

Portfolio

https://terryjavascript.github.io/profile/

SKILLS

LITAIL

H I IVIL	
CSS	••••
jQuery	••••
Bootstrap	••••
Media Query	••••
PHP/MySQL/AJAX	••••

LANGUAGES

Wordpress

English	••••
Korean	••••
Spanish	•••00

HOBBIES

TRAVELING, BASKETBALL, PHOTOGRAPHY, EATING

PROFILE

I am driven by exploration. I thrive in building experiences for myself and the people around me. I pride myself in my innate abilities to solve problems, improve circumstances, and turn ideas into projects. That is why I decided to change my career path from the banking industry to become a full stack web developer.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Freelance Web Designer, ENC-Inc.

Sep 2018 - Present

Designed and coded a website for an international logistic company using bootstrap and jQuery. Total time took about 6 weeks after going through the steps of company presentation, meetings, wireframe (mockflow), deployment preview (github), and updates.

Assistant Underwriter, Bank of Hope

Los Angeles

Torrance

Mar 2017 - Aug 2018

Underwriter for Commercial loans, Construction loans, and Real Estate loans. Promoted in April 2018 from Credit Analyst with a 2018 Portfolio of \$10.8MM.

International Protocol Executive Officer, FISU (International University Sports Federation)

Gwangju, Gyeonggido, Korea

Santa Barbara

Los Angeles

Jan 2015 - Aug 2015

Managed events and performed administrative duties for VIP and high executives such as the President of South Korea and significant members of international governments.

EDUCATION

University of California, Santa Barbara, Bachelor's Degree, International Studies

Sep 2012 - Jul 2016

UCLA Extension, Completion of Fullstack Bootcamp

Sep 2017 - Mar 2018

REFERENCES

Charles Kim from Bank of Hope

charlesxsungxkim@gmail.com | 562-760-1193

Joshua Lee from ENC Inc.

Younglee@enc-inc.net | 310-630-8001

